indianotes.com 2007-11-19

# Information Collection and Use The information you provide such as name

** Information Collection and Use**The  information you provide such as name, address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card number to process your order.  We use it to properly bill or credit your account and, if necessary, to follow up on your order of merchandise. We may use your information to keep you updated about our special deals and upon arrival of new items. But if you don't want us to send you about our deals you have every option to opt out.  

** Cookies  
**  
A "cookie" is very small text file placed on your hard drive by a Web Page server. It serves as your personal identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. It is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. The purpose of a "cookie" is to tell the server that you returned to that Web page. Of course, if you never register or leave personal information with indianotes.com, then the server only knows that someone with your cookie has returned to the Web site. You are in charge of deciding whether we know anything about you. 

When you come to our site or when you register with our site, we create your personal profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a "cookie," which is a very small bit of code. This code is uniquely yours. It enables us to know more about you, allows you to utilize some of our website's functionality, and correspond with us about your personal profile without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites. We use cookies to record session information, such as items that you added to your shopping cart and to conduct marketing tests on our Web pages. By showing how and when you use the site, cookies help us see which areas and products are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide better services to our visitors’  needs. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

** Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected . **We do our best to keep these informations safe and secure. **

** Special Deals**

Our members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.  **  
** Users who wish to no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out of our email listings by following the instructions in each email. 

** Notice**

We may change our privacy policy from time to time. All changes to this policy are effective after we provide you with at least thirty 30 days notice of the changes by posting the changes here in our  Site and sending an e-mail to users who have provided us their e-mail address for this purpose. We will give you 30 days time  to notify us if you don't agree to our new changes. 

** Disclaimer**

We do not sell, rent, or trade your personal information to any third party.

** Contact Info**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: admin@indianotes.com
